They're going deep undercover.
White Chicks is a comedy, crime film directed by Keenen Ivory Wayans.
Two FBI agent brothers, Marcus and Kevin
Copeland, accidentally foil a drug bust.
To avoid being fired they accept a mission escorting a pair of socialites to the
Hamptons--but when the girls are disfigured in a car accident, they refuse to go.
Left without options, Marcus and Kevin decide to pose as the sisters,
transforming themselves from black men into rich white women.
Kevin Copeland / Brittany Wilson, played by Shawn Wayans.
Marcus Anthony Copeland II / Tiffany Wilson, played by Marlon Wayans.
Elliott Gordon, played by Frankie Faison.
Latrell Spencer, played by Terry Crews.
Gina Copeland, played by Faune Chambers Watkins.
Denise Porter, played by Rochelle Aytes.
White Chicks (stylized as WHiTE CHiCKS) is a 2004 American buddy cop action comedy film directed by Keenen Ivory Wayans from a screenplay co-written by
Wayans, Xavier Cook, Andy McElfresh, Michael Anthony Snowden, with additional contributions by and starring Marlon Wayans and Shawn Wayans.
It also stars Jaime King, Frankie Faison, Lochlyn Munro, and John Heard.
In the film, two black FBI agent brothers go undercover as white women by using whiteface
to protect two hotel heiresses from a kidnapping plot targeting socialites.
Principal photography for White Chicks took place in Chilliwack and
Victoria in British Columbia, and in The Hamptons in New York.
It was theatrically released in the United States on June 23, 2004.
The film received generally mixed reviews upon release, and was nominated
for five Golden Raspberry Awards, including Worst Picture.
It grossed over $113.1 million worldwide, and has since
come to be regarded as a cult classic.
The film explores themes of undercover, kidnapping, fbi, auction, nightclub.
The tone is lighthearted.